# **Edivar O Ceadaigh Santos Junior**

# **IT Support | Business Administration | Software Developer**

4 Willow House, Red Arches Park, Baldoyle, Dublin 13
Phone: 089 976 1360
E-mail: junior\_scan16@hotmail.com
LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/edivarjunior

# **PROFILE**

I am a bilingual IT Support Agent and have recently completed a Graduate Diploma in Computing at Ulster University in partnership with Microsoft and Irish Times Training, focusing on Data Analytics. Through studying Computing, I have developed an in-depth understanding of data analysis and manipulation, information organisation and efficient project implementation. Also, following the development of new skills, I can relate my previous professional experience to provide an easier, more assertive and smoother work experience in order to improve results.

I have almost 2 years of experience in complex and challenging projects including the design of social networks and mapping company's database information. My passion relies in IT systems handling data, software, cloud computing and implementation. As a personal challenge I am developing a project to assist in controlling, mapping and analysing daily routine of cleaning schedules. The tool is designed to track the complete operations around professional cleaning services, collecting data at each function to enable analysis and reporting on time management, material and stock control, cost analysis and client communication to improve efficiencies and results.

As a Business Administrator, I learned the importance of properly designed and implemented systems to gain the best use of current technologies, supported by a skilled workforce. I commit to assist the development of business solutions and achieve the best possible result.

Visa status: Stamp 4: full permission to work

### SUMMARY OF EDUCATION AND SKILLS

- Programming: JAVA, HTML, CSS, SQL.
- Working with programs including Intelij, PhpAdmin, Xampp, Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, Android Studio and Azure, associated with tools such as GitHub, Vaadin and Maven.
- Operating systems: MacOS, Windows.
- Experience in customer service and client facing.
- Ability to work on initiative and support others, organized and attentive to detail.
- Proficient using Microsoft Office Suite including Microsoft Excel, Word, Power Point, Outlook and Internet Explorer.
- Success in working on complex projects using a collaborative work model.
- Participation in the implementation project, customisation and validation of ERP X-CLINIC, involving the mapping of processes linked to the areas of Patient Details, Purchasing, Billing and creating Management Reports.
- Manage stock levels and material orders.
- Ongoing analysis of indirect costs using ABC Cost methodology.
- Procurement activities with experience in quoting for supplies and services and manage the contracts.
- Key Logistics procedures such as Stock maintenance using the "EOQ" method, routing and freight quotes and supplier development.
- Analytical thinking, problem solving, and object-oriented design.
- Team leader skills.

# **EDUCATION**

# ULSTER UNIVERSITY 2017-2019/Dublin, Ireland

## Level 8 Graduate Diploma in Computing (Data Analytics)

Main areas: Server-side, Cloud, Programming.

Core modules: Software Development (Java, SQL), Database Systems, Data Structure, Cloud Development.

# FUNDACAO GETULIO VARGAS UNIVERSITY Level 9 master's in Logistics and Supply Chain Management (incomplete)

2011-2012/Sao Paulo, Brazil

Main areas: Supply Chain, Internal Logistics, Reverse Logistics.

Core modules: Strategic Logistics Planning, Financial Math, Global Logistics, Demand and Stock Management, Integrated Management Systems and Electronic Business, Supplier Development and Material Acquisition, Logistic Costs, Planning, Control and Evaluation of Logistic Projects.

## Level 8 Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration - UNIVERSITY UNIGRANRIO

Main areas: Human Resources, Logistics, Strategic Planning and Controlling.

Core modules: Strategic Planning, Human Resources, Financial and Budget Administration, Cost Analysis, Accounting, Marketing, Financial Mathematics, Statistics, Decision Process, Logistics.

Final Year Project: The recruiting, selection and training process for people on entry level.

### ADDITIONAL COURSES

Java Diploma
 HTML and CSS
 Developing Supervisory Skills
 The Development of Projects for Funding
 Financial Control
 Financial Planning and Analysis
 IACT-Dublin
 Aramark-Dublin
 SENAC-Brazil
 SENAC-Brazil
 SENAC-Brazil

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SAP 2018 – Present/ Dublin, Ireland

### IT Service Desk Agent

- Full-time responsibility for troubleshooting internal user issues related to:

**HR** – Review user roles and profiles, add and remover permissions and assist in the correct completion of data entry with the user, insuring timely resolution of their issues.

**Finance** – Analyse and understand requests for assistance from accounts teams in relation to generating, modifying and deleting invoices.

**Concur** – Technical troubleshooting of travel and expenses of employees, investigate the root cause of the user's problem. **LSO** – Investigate the reasons why applications for courses are not processed in the system, including the review of company codes and correct allocation of employees.

**ACT** – Code-check timesheets to ensure the correct allocation to cost centres and cost objects, setting user permission appropriately and troubleshooting timesheets that have not been correctly rooted for approval.

- Training of new service desks agents in ACT.
- Previously also trained and worked in the following areas of:
   Portal Webpage, Ariba, IDM, IDS, Jira, People@SAP, Jam, ARM
- Directly liaising with system users to quickly and effectively resolve IT problems or identify complex issues to be escalated to the next level.

Apple 2018 – 2018 / Dublin, Ireland

# Technical Support (AHA - At Home Advisor)

- Full-time responsibility for troubleshooting customers issues related to iPhone, iPad, iPod Touch.
- First point of contact between Apple and customer.
- Assist the customer for solution, refer to specific area for further assistance or schedule product for repair.

# **Aramark Workplace Solutions**

2015 - 2018/ Dublin, Ireland

# **Cleaner Supervisor**

- Spot Award Front line first.
- Full-time responsibility for supervision of cleaning staff team.
- Staff rosters and completion of timesheets to return to Head Office.
- Stocktake and material ordering, and implementation of stock monitoring system.
- Liaise directly with St Johns management on required daily tasks.
- Working close with elderly residence and ensuring a clean and safe environment for them.
- Produce procedure document and checklists to ensure highest standers of cleaning are maintained.
- Encourage feedback from building users and staff on their satisfaction of our services and suggested improvements from our team.

#### Floor Staff

- Glass collecting.
- Cleaning the Venue at the end.
- Reorganizing stock.
- Cash Desk door security.

# **ULTIMATE FIT TRADE GYM EQUIPMENTS**

2011 -2013/ Sao Paulo, Brazil

# **Logistics Analyst**

- Customer service and client facing.
- The strategic purchasing of weight training and cardio equipment including planning, organization and control of the equipment purchased in the Health & Fitness industry
- Quotation and selection of suppliers (split-shipping) for sending equipment nationwide. Follow-through of planned purchases based on sales ("Just in time").
- Stock control of a minimum inventory. Control "Days on Hand" (days of inventory available). The negotiation with and approval of suppliers and direct negotiation and sale of equipment.

# BLUE CROSS HOSPITAL

2010 -2011/ Sao Paulo, Brazil

# **Hospital Accounts Assistant**

- Customer service and client facing.
- Hospital billing / invoicing and administration duties relating to the care provided to Accident & Emergency patients.

### DIAGNOSTIC CENTER AND IMAGE SCAN LAGOS

2000 -2010/Rio de Janeiro, Brazil

# **Administration Supervisor**

- Customer service and client facing.
- Prepare documentation and liaise with Health insurance providers to process patient's treatment claims.
- Ensure payments are received in full and reconciled with the patient's accounts or pre-authorization received if required.
- Analysis and preparation of a purchase scheme based on demand.
- Planning and implementation of a unified medical system called X-Clinic.
- Responsible for purchasing and inventory (FIFO Scheme), assessment of and negotiation with new suppliers of office equipment.
- Supervision of staff in the Admin and Reception area with six reporting to me on Admin and IT issues.

# LANGUAGES

ENGLISH PORTUGUESE SPANISH
Professional Native Elementary
Working Proficiency Proficiency Proficiency

## **INTERESTS**

- I am interested in everything related to innovation and technology.
- Passionate about Health and Fitness, I enjoy hill walking and hiking in the countryside.
- I enjoy popular culture including film and music and spend some time relaxing to watch the latest movie releases.
- I am also a keen computer gamer if I have some free time.

# REFERENCES

On request.